Because, you see... the Ripple is naturally channeled through water!
やはり 拳で接触して 直接
太陽の波紋を送り込まねば！
This is it! Turquoise Blue Overdrive!
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)ディオ様が
我に生命を与えくださり➡
この男と 戦わせてくれたことに
感謝と この上ない名誉を感じる｡
Jo-!
Jojo!
H-He did it!
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)
この男は 勇者の素質 十分！➡
This isn't over!
もう 水中という ハンデの上での
戦いは 終わりだ！➡
I never expected he would reach the surface at the same speed as the Ripple...
今度は 能力と能力！
技と技！ 精神と精神！
What speed... The Overdrive only grazed Bruford's forehead!
貴様！ 最大を尽くし
この ブラフォードと戦え！
It looks like I'll have to deliver the Ripple of the sun with a full-contact punch after all!
URYYYYAHHH！
《ディオに 操られながらも
生前の誇りを忘れてはいない！➡
Master Dio! I offer my eternal gratitude for being revived,
as well as the chance to fight this child!
そして その誇りは
戦うことへの 暴力への誇り！》
貴様の血を
この肉体の 一部としてやる！
He is worthy to bear the title of a true warrior!
また 髪の毛攻撃か！ 来い！
We shall no longer hold ourselves back within the confines of underwater battle!
今度は たっぷり
波紋を流し込んでやる！
なっ‼
Let this be a battle of strength versus strength!
Skill versus skill! Cunning versus cunning!
♬(ｵｰﾌﾟﾆﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
You whelp! Prove that you can stand up in battle against the mighty Bruford!
Wrryyyyyy!
♬ 空 こぼれ落ちたふたつの星が
Even under Dio's influence, he still has the same pride he had until the day he died!
And that pride is rooted in his respect for intense battling!
♬ 光と闇の水面
吸い込まれてゆく
I'll take your blood and make it my own!
He's attacking with his hair again?!
♬ 引き合うように 重なる波紋
Have at it! This time I'll send my Ripple right through it!
♬～
♬ 誇りの道を往く者に
太陽の導きを
♬ 野望の果てを目指す者に
生け贄を
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
♬～
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
♬ 震えるほど心
燃え尽きるほど熱く
♬ その手から放て 鼓動
Editer:
Tonitonichopchop
♬ 身体 漲る勇気で
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
♬ 迷いなき覚悟に喝采を
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
♬ その血の運命 ジョジョ
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
♬～
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Raw Hunter:
WRRRRY
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 6: "Courage of Tomorrow"
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)はあっ！
オーバードライブ連打‼
Overdrive Barrage!
ぐぅぅぅッ！
ぐぁぁぁぁッ！
Jojo!
ジョジョ～！
ぐええッ！
This is bad... A Ripple can only flow outward from the limbs!
ま… まずい！
波紋は 手や足など➡
末端部分からしか 出せない｡
If he's tied up and unable to move his arms,
he won't be able to use his Ripple to cut that hair!
あのように
がんじがらめにされては➡
両腕が使えず
波紋で髪を切断するのは 不可能！
E-Even if we try to help him, we've already got our hands full!
た… 助けに行きたくても
俺たちの前には 今…｡
Tarkus, you brute!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
タルカス こ… こいつが！
ぐぁぁぁッ！
H-His hair is piercing through my clothes and eating into my skin...
《ふ… 服を破り 僕の皮膚に
じかに 食い込んでいる！➡
...and the more I struggle, the stronger it gets!
もがけば もがくほど強く！
髪の毛が 僕の血を吸っている！》
He's draining my blood through his hair!
ぐああ…｡
This is the end, young warrior!
とどめだ～！ 若者よ～！
I'll slice off your head and drink from the fountain of blood!
首をはねて
その あふれる血をもらうぞ！
That's it!
これだ～！
ここぉぉぉぉぉおお！
おりゃああああああ！
The Ripple that flows through steel...
鋼を伝わる波紋疾走！
ﾒﾀﾙｼﾙﾊﾞｰｵｰﾊﾞｰﾄﾞﾗｲﾌﾞ！
Metal Silver Overdrive!
B-Brilliant! He was able to defend himself from the sword and deliver the Ripple with the same technique!
う… うまい！ 剣からの防御が➡
イコール
波紋攻撃に つながっているぞ！
震えるぞハート！
燃え尽きるほどヒート‼
My heart is burning...
...with the heat of a raging fire!
おおおおおっ！
刻むぞ 血液のビート！
Feel the pounding beat of my pulse!
Sunlight Yellow Overdrive!
サンライトイエロー
オーバードライブ！
ぐおっ！
He did it! That's the sound of the Ripple when it makes full contact!
おおっ！
やった この音！
いつも聞く 波紋の流れる音だ！
《い… 今までの亡者とは違った男
ブラフォード｡➡
Th-This man was nothing like the savages I've fought so far...
Bruford... he still had his wits about him, and a sense of his past...
彼の生い立ちと
その精神を知っているだけに…｡➡
でも これでいい！➡
Regardless, it's better this way... He's a zombie that preys on humankind, giving rise to more monsters!
彼も 人間の血を吸い
牙にかけ 仲間を増やすゾンビ｡➡
He must be defeated!
倒さなくてはならないんだ！》
I am... the Black Knight, Bruford!
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)
俺は… 黒騎士ブラフォード！
これしきの痛み へこたれぬわ！
This pain means nothing to me!
見苦しいぜ ブラフォード！
You're pathetic, Bruford!
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)ウゴォー！
Even reduced so low, your bloodlust as a zombie forces you to keep attacking!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
そんなに 醜くなってまでもよ！➡
ゾンビとしての殺意が消えず
襲ってくるなんてよ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)何!?
ジョースターさん 何している！➡
What?!
Mr. Joestar, what are you doing?!
Move or he'll strike you down! Why won't you move?!
かわすか 攻撃するかしろ！
なぜ 動かない!?
一体 これは!?
What is this...
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)２人とも 一体!?
What are they doing?!
あなたは 今
｢これしきの痛み｣と言った｡
You said before... the pain was nothing to you.
Pain... You can feel pain again.
｢痛み｣と…｡
あなたは 痛みを感じている！
F-Flowers...
は… 花だ｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ブラフォードの足元に｡
They're blooming at Bruford's feet!
黒騎士ブラフォードの肉体は
波紋を食らったことによって➡
After being struck by the Ripple, the Black Knight Bruford's body is starting to crumble.
崩れつつある｡
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)ぐっ！
But at the same time, he can feel pain once again...
だが 同時に
痛みを取り戻している！
つまり 人間としての痛みを！
The same pain that once made him human!
波紋は 彼のゾンビとしての肉体を
滅ぼすと同時に➡
The Ripple has destroyed his zombified body, but it has also resurrected his noble soul!
高潔な人間としての魂を
よみがえらせたのだ｡
だから 僕は
あなたとの戦いを止めた｡
That's why I stopped fighting...
That's why you didn't follow through with your sword...
だから あなたは
剣の攻撃を途中で止めた｡
His face!
あの顔は！ さっきまでの怒りと
憎しみにゆがんだ顔ではない！
It isn't twisted with anger or resentment anymore!
母親と会話する 息子のように
安らいでいる顔だ！
It's gentle, like the face of a boy as he talks to his mother!
You... thought I was going to halt my strike?
(ﾌﾞﾗﾌｫｰﾄﾞ)お前…
俺が 途中で 剣撃を止めると｡➡
そこまで信用して
攻撃してこなかったのか｡➡
You were really so sure I wouldn't retaliate?
そこまで
人間を信用できるのか｡➡
Do you really have such faith in others?
ぐあっ！➡
フフフ…
この痛みこそ 生の証し｡
This pain is the burden of the living...
この痛み あればこそ
喜びも 感じることができる｡
A pain that serves to contrast with the rare moments of pure joy in life.
これが 人間か｡➡
I suppose that is the meaning of humanity.
I feel a bizarre sense of peace right now...
奇妙な安らぎを
俺は 今 感じる｡➡
I no longer feel resentment for this world.
もう世への恨みはない｡➡
Having met such an astounding man...
Such a warm human-being...
こんな 素晴らしい男に
こんな 温かい人間に➡
Meeting a person like you before my end will finally allow me to join my queen.
最後の最後に 出会えたから｡
我が女王の元へ 旅立とう｡
My friend from a world three centuries beyond my own... tell me your name.
300年たった世界の友人よ｡
お前の名を 聞かせてくれ｡
ジョナサン･ジョースター｡
Jonathan Joestar.
Jonathan...
ジョナサン 我が女王より賜った➡
I wish upon you the same blessing that is engraved on this sword, bestowed unto me by my Queen...
この剣に刻んである言葉を
捧げよう！➡
Good Fortune
Luck!
LUCK！➡
...and let this guide you towards your destiny...
そして 君の未来へ
これを持って行け！➡
Courage!
Pluck!
PLUCK！
Bruford!
ブラフォード！
フフ…｡
What a tragedy... What a bizarre fate!
何という皮肉
何という奇妙な運命！
To have the only salvation for your soul come when faced with death...
そんな！ 魂を救うために
殺さなくてはいけないなんて！
Even as he embraced death while cursing the world,
he had such pride!
恨みを持って 処刑されたとはいえ
こんな 誇り高い人物を！
高貴なる 心の持ち主を！
どす黒い狂気に変える！
That terrible stone mask! It was responsible for changing him into an absolute madman!
憎むべきは 石仮面！
No matter what... I'm not going to forgive you for this, Dio!
許せないのは それを操るディオ！
Jojo! Behind you!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョジョ～！ 後ろだ！
Tarkus!
タルカス！
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)ふん…｡
H-How could you?!
な… なんと！
How could you shatter Bruford's armor like that?!
You just hearlessly crushed it into dust!
友人ブラフォードの
遺品とも呼べる かっちゅうを➡
無情にも 粉みじんにするとは！
Bruford was a coward!
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)
ブラフォードの腰抜けが！➡
I may have respected him,
but he was nothing more than a strategist!
尊敬してはいたが
所詮 技士にすぎぬ男｡➡
I yearn for the day I can become an elite slaughterer!
だが 俺は
殺りくのエリートを目指した｡
My strength... will bring death and destruction to all!
力で殺しまくり
破壊しつくすだけだ！
絶望の悲鳴を発せ！
MUOOOHHHH！
Now let me hear your cries of despair!
ぬわっ！
う… うわっ うわぁぁぁぁ！
Nice catch, Jojo!
ナイスキャッチ ジョジョ！
が… 崖が崩れるぞ！
The cliff is collapsing!
この葉っぱ！ ジョジョ！
はい！
These leaves...
Jojo!
Right!
Life Force Magnetism Overdrive!
生命磁気への オーバードライブ！
UOHHHHH！
つかまれ！
スピードワゴン！ ポコ！
Grab on, Speedwagon, Poco!
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)〈人間の体は
微量ながら 磁気を帯びており➡
Within every human being, there exists a very faint trace of a magnetic field...
生命磁石になっていると
考えられる｡➡
By using an Overdrive, this inherent magnetism can be greatly powered up!
オーバードライブは
その生命磁気を パワーアップ！➡
By letting that Ripple flow into the leaves, they too become living magnets!
木の葉に それを流し込み
葉っぱ自体を➡
生命磁石として
くっつけたのだ！〉
Amazing!
すげえ！
Yay!
や～い！
(ポコ)こんなこと できるなんて！
兄ちゃんたち まさか 人間なの？
How are you doing this?! Are you folks even human?
Or are you some kinda angels sent down from heaven?!
それとも 天から降りてきた
神様の使い？
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)まったくだぜ！
常識が マヒしちまって➡
He's got a point!
I've grown so used to this madness, I've quit questioning it.
疑問にも思わなかったが➡
But there's one mystery I'd still like to see answered!
一番の謎は あんただぜ！
ツェペリのおっさん｡➡
Old man Zeppeli, where in the world did you learn to do all of this?!
あんたは 一体 どこで
こんなこと覚えたんだ？
I met a rather curious fellow in a port town in India...
《わしは インドの港町で
１人の 奇妙な男と出会った》
He claimed to be a doctor, but he appeared far too young and ragged for that to be true.
《そうと見えないほど
若く みすぼらしいのに➡
自分を 医者だというのだ！➡
わしは驚いた｡ 西洋医学では
切断しなければならない➡
I was shocked!
On that fateful day, he radiated a bright light which healed a leg that would have required amputation with conventional medicine!
腐りかけの足を 光を放つ手で
治療してみせたのだ》
The power he used was that of the Ripple!
《その力こそ 波紋だったのだ！➡
I realized I could use the Ripple to help defend against the maleficence of the stone mask....
波紋の力ならば
石仮面の最悪の事態に➡
対抗できると感じた わしは➡
チベットの ヌーと呼ばれる川を
上流へ 上流へと登り➡
...so I journeyed further along the Salween River into Tibet, seeking the man whom taught that doctor...
その医者の師に 会いに行った》
《名は トンペティ》
His name... was Tompetty.
Wanderer from afar, I can see your future...
(ﾄﾝﾍﾟﾃｨ)《遠方から来た者よ
そなたの 未来が見える｡➡
You have come seeking knowledge... but be warned, should you move forward, your destiny will forever be changed.
そなた
ここで 修行するつもりか？➡
すれば 運命が大きく変わり➡
Your fate will only lead to death.
死への宿命を
背負うことになるぞ！》
Very well.
《構いません｡ 私には
命を賭して学ぶ 理由がある！》
I have a cause that I am more than willing to die for.
The prophecy foretold by my teacher, Tompetty...
《我が師 トンペティの予言…｡➡
これは ジョジョにも
誰にも言えない秘密よ》
I can't tell Jojo, or anyone else...
Old man?
おっさん？
W-What's that sound? Is it from the Ripple?
こ… この音…｡
この音も 波紋の音なのか？
N-No!
ち… 違う！
It's Tarkus!
(ポコ)タルカスだ！
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)ゴババァ！
Wrryyyyyyy!
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)URYYYYY！
む… 無茶なやつだ！
H-He's a madman! He threw himself at us from that height?!
あの高さから
身を投げて 突っ込んでくるとは！
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)ぐおっ！
This glider is filled with the Life Force Magnetism Ripple!
このグライダーは
生命磁気の波紋の魂よ！
What did he expect would happen?
触れれば 当然 そうなるわ！
あれは？
Look!
T-That's the knights' old training grounds!
(ポコ)昔の騎士たちの修錬場だよ｡
Jump down there, before he makes us crash into the ground!
あそこへ 飛び移れ！
地面に たたきつけられるぞ！
(ポコ)ひえええっ！
ぐおっ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)タルカスのやつ
あの高さから 石壁へ直撃か！
Tarkus slammed straight into that stone wall!
いくら ゾンビとはいえ
骨肉は バラバラじゃろう｡
Zombie or not, that must have destroyed his body!
仮面をかぶった ディオとは違い➡
And unlike Dio, he didn't wear the stone mask!
His body can't regenerate, so there's no way he's still moving.
肉体の再生能力はないから
もう動けんはず！
W-What a monster... His obsession with battle keeps him moving...
な… なんてやつだ！
まさに 戦うことが生きがいか！
...even though his bones should be completely shattered!
骨は ボキボキに
砕けているはずなのに｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)登ってくる！
He's climbing up!
Our priority is defeating Dio, but if he's going to chase us, we won't have a choice.
我々の目的は
まず ディオを倒すことだが➡
追ってくるなら しかたあるまい｡
タルカスのやつを
ここで 片付ける！
We'll deal with Tarkus first!
Jojo! Get that boy to safety inside!
ジョジョ！ その がきんちょを
建物の中へ避難させろ｡
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)うおお～｡
There's something strange about this door... It doesn't feel right.
何だ？ この扉は！
おかしな手応え！
き… 気を付けて！ ここは
騎士たちの 殺人修練場の遺跡！➡
B-Be careful!
This is where the Knights used to train for their battles!
いろんな仕掛けがあるって
うわさだよ！
I've heard this place is full of traps!
Mr. Joestar! Something's coming for you!
ジョースターさん！
何か 出てくるぞ！
ぐあっ！ ぐぐ…｡
Mister!
兄ちゃん！
ジョジョ！
Jojo!
T-This is...
こ… これは！
...Tarkus!
タルカス！
う～む… 懐かしい｡➡
How nostalgic...
...The Chamber of the Two-Headed Dragon's Chain Death Match...
双首竜の間
チェーンデスマッチ｡➡
It's been three hundred years since I've been here... I shall Indulge.
300年ぶりに やってみるか｡
This is one of many chambers where the medieval knights would hone their deadly skills!
〈ここは
中世騎士 殺人修練場の１つ！➡
The Chamber of the Two Headed Dragon, home to the Chained Neck Death Match!
双首竜の間！
チェーンネックデスマッチ！〉
I have taken 48 lives in here... You will find I am quite skilled at it.
48人を葬った わしの
最も得意とする競技の１つよ｡
G-Give it a rest, old man Zeppeli! It's too thick!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)や… やめてくれ！
ﾂｪﾍﾟﾘのおっさん！ 分厚すぎるぜ！
O-Oh no... His knuckles are torn ragged!
ひ… ひでえ｡ あのおじさん
拳が あんなになるまで｡
Unfortunately, the Ripple was never intended to be used as a tool for destruction...
は… 波紋法は 悔しいことに
破壊を目的としたものではない｡
レンガ程度は 割れても
このドアは 破壊できん｡
A small rock can be broken, but this door is far stronger than that.
したがって
ジョジョも わし同様➡
Even worse, Jojo will run into the same problem...
あのチェーンを切断することは
不可能なのだ！
He won't be able to break those chains!
貴様の その首輪
外すことのできる鍵は…｡
The only way out of that collar is the key...
The one in my collar!
ここに 付いておる｡
The door cannot be opened from the outside during a match...
扉は 試合中 外から
開かないようになっているし➡
俺の首輪を外す鍵は
お前の首輪にある｡
...and the key for each man's shackles is contained in his opponent's collar!
Which means the only one who will leave this room...
つまり 相手の首をふっ飛ばして
勝った者のみが…｡
ぐうっ！
自由となれるルールよ！
...is the one who can rip off the head of his opponent first!
おおおおおおっ！
オーバードライブ！
Overdrive!
うっ ううっ!?
うう… あっ！
チェ… チェーンが
天井に 接触しているので➡
T-The chain is attached to the ceiling, so the Ripple disperses before it can even reach Tarkus!
波紋が散って
タルカスまで流れていかない！
ぐお～！
ふん！
《ぐあ～っ！ ぐぐっ…｡➡
上腕の骨に ひびが入ったか｡➡
He broke my arm!
ぐ… この応急手当は 波紋の
生命エネルギーで行うとして➡
I could heal it with the Ripple's life-giving energy...
何とかしなくてはならないのは➡
...but first I need to do something about the collar crushing my neck... it's keeping me... from breathing properly!
気管を潰そうとしている
この首輪！➡
呼吸ができん！》
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)うう！ くうっ！
ジョジョ～！
Jojo!
Damn it! D-did I just wet my pants?!
(ポコ)
ちくしょう！ い… いつの間にか
ズボンをぬらしちまった｡
I-I need to get away from these people...
も… もう嫌だ｡
この人たちといるのは！
この人たちは おいらたちの町に
災いを運んできやがった｡
They're the ones who brought this disaster on our town!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ツェペリさん あのレバーだ！➡
Mr. Zeppeli, that lever...
I think the door only opens from the inside!
この扉 中からしか
開けられんようになってるらしい｡
Jojo may be willing to fight one on one,
but he's sure to be exhausted after defeating Bruford.
ジョジョは
１人でも 戦うだろうが➡
ブラフォードを倒し
体力の消耗が激しい！
We have to find some way to get in there and help him, no matter what it takes!
どんな方法でもいい｡
中へ入って 力を合わせねば！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
くっ 入れそうな所なんてないぜ｡
I don't see any other way in there!
(ポコ)あっ…｡
It's too small...
(ポコ)《小さすぎる｡➡
おっさんたちじゃ
あそこから入ることはできない｡➡
These guys could never fit through there...
でも… おいらなら》
But...
...I can.
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)URRRRRYYYYYY！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)くそっ！
扉が開かないのなら しかたない｡
Damn it!
If we can't get the door open, then we're out of options!
絶壁の下の タルカスの入った
明かり窓から入るしかない！
We'll have to go through the entrance
that Tarkus used further down!
But that will take too long!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)行くまでに
時間が かかり過ぎるぜ！
だが 他に方法はない！
We have no other choice!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)うっ！ ううっ…｡➡
俺は いつも傍観者よ｡➡
I'm always watching everyone from the sidelines...
何もできねえ 何もしてやれねえ｡
I can never do anything to help!
Hey, Poco... Look at me!
(少年１)
《おいポコ！ ちゃんと見ろ！➡
Look at me when I'm talking to you!
俺の顔を
ちゃんと見ろってんだよ！》
The little brat's scared out of his wits!
(少年２)
《こいつ ビビっとるぜ！》
(少年３)
《歯 ガタガタいってやがるぜ！》
He's shakin' like a leaf!
Would you look at that!
(少年４)《ほれ～！ ほれよ！》
He's gonna cry!
(少年１)《泣き出すぜ こいつ》
《うがっ！》
(少年たちの笑い声)
H-Hey!
(少年３)《お… おい！》
(少年４)《うわ！》
(少年２)《ヤベえぜ 逃げろ！》
That's enough, let's scram!
S-Sis...
《ね… 姉ちゃん》
They were bullying you again, weren't they?
(ポコの姉)《あんた また
やられっぱなしだったのね》
It's just sad. Why don't you fight back for once?
(ポコの姉)
《あきれるわ｡ なぜ いつも
黙ってて やり返さないのよ？》
《あ… あした やってやらあ！》
I... I will... tomorrow!
And yet tomorrow never comes...
(ポコの姉)
《あしたって いつのあしたよ？》
《あ… あしたさ》
I-I mean it!
(ポコの姉)《ポコ あんたの
一番怖いことって何？》
Poco...
What really scares you the most?
Is the pain what you're really afraid of?
《一番怖いのは この痛みなの？➡
Is that what frightens you so much?
痛いのって 怖い？》
(ポコの姉)
《あんた いつまでも…｡➡
You think that pain is scary...
大人になっても
１人じゃ 何にもできない方が➡
What about the thought of growing up to be powerless? Doesn't that scare you even more?!
もっと怖いとは 思わないの？》
《うっ お… 俺… お…》
I-I...
There, there, crybaby...
(ポコの姉)《ほらほら 弱虫さん》
(ポコの姉)《うち帰って
姉さんが 洗濯したげる》
Let's go home and get those clothes cleaned up, okay?
(ポコ)《うっうっうっ…》
≪(物音)
Poco!
ポコ!?
A window?!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)明かり窓!?
H-Hey! Are you trying to get in through there?!
お… おい！
あそこから 入るつもりか！
Stop, you fool!
やめろ バカ！
Stop him! Even if he manages to get inside,
Tarkus will have no qualms with killing a little boy!
止めるんだ！ あんな
年端もいかない 普通の人間が➡
部屋に入ったら 十中八九
タルカスに殺されてしまうぞ！
小僧！ 行くんじゃねえ 危険だ！
Kid, what are you doing?! It's too dangerous!
T-Think about what happened when
those monsters attacked last time...
《も… 亡者どもが 町へ
行ったときのことを考えるんだ｡➡
あの でっかい兄ちゃんが
死んじまったら 町が襲われる！》
If that big man dies, then who's gonna protect the town?
《姉ちゃんが襲われる！》
Who's gonna save my sister?!
I'm doing this... to protect my sister!
(ポコ)《姉ちゃんを守るのは
この おいらだ！》
姉ちゃん！ あしたって 今さ！
Sis! Tomorrow comes today!
Get back! It's dangerous!
来るな！ 危ない！
UYYYURRRYY！
Wrryyyy!
決闘の邪魔は 許さん！
Don't interfere with our duel!
おあああああっ！
(ポコ)ぐあっ！
(ﾂｪﾍﾟﾘ･ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)うわぁぁぁ～っ！
ポコ～！
Poco!
(ポコ)
こ… 怖いのは 痛みじゃあないぜ｡
I-I'm not... afraid... of a little pain...
(ポコ)ヘヘヘ…｡
(鍵が開く音)
やったぜ！ ヘヘヘ…｡
I... did it...
That was incredible, Poco...
立派だぜ ポコ｡
心配はない｡ 傷は浅いぜ！
Don't worry... Your injuries aren't too severe.
Old man Zeppeli, make this animal pay for what he's done!
ツェペリの旦那！
思いっきし やっつけてやれ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)旦那？
Sir?
Your fate will only lead to death.
(ﾄﾝﾍﾟﾃｨ)《そなたは 死への宿命を
背負うことになるぞ》
ついに… ついに来たか｡
あの予言のときが｡
Well... the time has finally come, as it was foretold...
えっ？
If this is to be my destiny... then I will embrace it without regrets.
これが運命なら
あるがまま 受け入れよう｡
ツェペリさん！
あんた 今 何て…？
Mr. Zeppeli!
What... did... you just say?
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
♬ I'll be the roundabout
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
♬ I spend the day away
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬～
The music dance and sing
♬ The music dance and sing
♬ They make
the children really ring
They make the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
♬ Spend the day away
♬ Call it morning
driving through
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬ In and around the lake
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
and they stand there
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
♬ I'll be there with you
There with you
♬～
Next Episode
This... is just too cruel!
You'll pay for this, Tarkus!
I'll smash you to a pulp!
Jojo...
Inherit my will!
Episode 7:
"Sorrowful Successor"
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
こんなこと 残酷すぎる！
許さん！ タルカス～！
(ﾀﾙｶｽ)ズタボロと化せ～！
ジョジョ！ 継いでくれ！
わしの意志を！
＜改ざんＢ－ＣＡＳカードによる
不正視聴は➡
刑法により禁じられた犯罪行為＞
＜５年以下の懲役 または➡
50万円以下の
罰金に処せられます＞
＜後悔しても 元には戻せない＞
不正視聴!?